I'm on Enoshima!
One thing if you please, look back only at me
Keep glowing
First Are you ready?
Pan-pan-pan-pan, these feelings
I'm very sorry
I'm very sorry I see the present in front of me
Into the future
Hold on to that voice
Promise me, with you
Wave to me from now on
Hot summer forever
I'm getting tired!
It hasn't even been five minutes!
I'm tired!
I'm so tired!
Oh no!
My side hurts.
It's hopeless!
No, I'm fast! One hour and ten minutes on that mountain road is seriously amazing!
It's really frustrating!
No, it's good!
Yes, I know, it's not easy to run by myself
It was tough to run alone in silence.
I think that was the toughest part.
I knew there is a difference between running alone and running with others.
I would like to express my gratitude to the people who support me, like my family, the members, and the staff.
the staff, and the fans who are involved with us.
I realized that I can't do it alone.
I'm going to put my gratitude into words more and more every day.
Oh my God, I'm so thirsty.
Oh no!Oh my God!
There was a huge, different view-like difference, but it was when we were stopped.
I ran 2 kilometers separately.
This means 5 more times, which is a bit much.
I'm not super good at running, but I'm sure this will help me build up my fitness for the future, so I'll do my best!
Thank you very much!
Achy!
Just a little more to go!
Hang in there! Hang in there!
You can do it!
Go, go, go!
Hang on!
Go for it!
Wow!
It's hot!
Oh, no!
It's so red.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Come on!
Train line 3 is coming up.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's meet again
Good luck, Miyu!
I'm going to go halfway.
I'm off!
See you later!
Bye bye, miss you all!
Bye bye bye
Good luck!Come on!
It's a good base!
I want to live on a good base!
Go!
For me too, Love One has really changed my world.
Since I joined Love One, every day is a new world for me.
So it's like a movie.
It's like a movie of my life.
You, my fans, are a part of me now.
I can't live without them.
You make me happy all the time.
You make everything worthwhile.
You are everything!
That's why I'm going to do my best to reach everyone!
It's so hot!
It's too much!
I need to drink water!
I'm so rattled, my whole body is rattled.
It's really cool!
It's fun, it's really fun!
There you go.
This is the hottest time of the day.
It's amazing!
Matsukura, I'll do my best.
I trust you, Matsukura.
I believe in you, Matsuda.
I believe in you too, Matsukura.
You can do it, Matsukura.
I'll do my best, Matsukura. Have fun.
Matsukura, you can walk if you want.
Matsuda, next is Amu-kun.
Matsuda, this is Amu-kun with pink hair.Matsuda: Amu-kun is a stiff, pink-haired Amu-kun.
Matsuda: So, I'd like to connect Amu-kun with
Matsuda I'd like to connect Watanabe.
Matsuda Oh no, it's almost over!
Matsuda Good luck!
Matsuda I'm on it, I'm on it.
Matsuda, let's go!
Matsukura, it was so hot!
Oh, shit!
Matsukura I can't wait to go!
Matsuda, they're here!
Matsukura, hang in there!
Matsukura Wow!
Matsukura, we're here.
Oh, my God! Yeah!
Go! Have fun!
It just started.
I feel great and refreshed!
I'm going to do my best!
Here we go.
Wait, it's over!
Yay!
How do you feel now that you've run 10 kilometers? New metch.
It was worse than I thought it would be.
The sun was hitting me in the eyes and all over my body
I felt like I was the sun!
It was too hot.It was too hot.
This line of "I'm sorry, but it was hard! It was fun!
It was amazing, Miyu!
It was fun to be relative to you.
It was fun the whole time!
How did your voice grow so long?
It was fun!
This is the first time for me to run seriously.
This is the first time I've run 10km, so I'm a bit nervous.
I'll do my best to pass the baton to the next good position.
I'm going to give it my all and run as hard as I can to pass the baton to the next good position.
Wow! There it is! It's in focus!
Come on!
Thank you for watching!
Oh, man.
My feet are killing me, right here. It's bad here. It hurts here.
It hurts here. It's a little painful.
Wow, whoever went 10 km did it.
I'm really going for it. I'm halfway there. I'm going for the last spurt.
Wow. Ouch. Ouch.
I can finally meet everyone.
Good work!
I'm really tired.
Take care and hang in there.
How's it going? Hey, Abun.
Your legs are really painful.
Keep it up!
I'm almost halfway there, but I think I can make it.
We're almost halfway there.
We're almost to the last cart.
Almost halfway.Already halfway there.
Now this hurts.
May I have your attention, please?
If it hurts when I push, it hurts like this.
It hurts.
No, it's fine, I got it.
I'm not pushing it, I'm not pushing it.
Cool!
Let me run.
Can you run?
I can run.
I'm serious.
It doesn't count.
Let me go.
Oh, my God, it's so easy.
If this starts to hurt...
I'm sorry, I get it.
There's a real chance we could get separated.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I'll leave it to you.
Kaito Miyachika, if you learn to do this, you can do it.
See you later.
Good luck!
Anpanman
Amerika
Go for it!
Well, we've started the next half round!
Well, you know, it's different when the members come to pick you up at the break point and when they don't cheer you on.
I feel so much better without their support.
I feel much better now!
Thank you for your hard work!Thank you for your hard work!
The staff has obviously been working on a tourism battery and other videos for our 주 video target.
I would also like to present a video with some ideas
Anyone who can help with the video would be appreciated!
Thank you very much!
Well, yes, we really are that
One Love Heart is a new organization.
We are going to work with 9 members from now on.
I think the unity of the nine of us...
The nine of us are cooperating together, and we are working in harmony.
and the meaning of working as a group.
I really hope that we, One Love Heart, can give hope to various groups and people.
I believe that we, One Love Heart, have been able to give hope to various groups and people.
Just a little more
Pork belly is première llaolan
I'll do my best!
I come from this way, I go that way.
Just go straight.
It takes an hour by train,
He said stop a little bit down the road.
Almost there.
Pushcorn!
Oh, here it comes!
Here it comes!
They're here!
They're waiting!
Hey!
Oh, no! Oh, no! I'm getting nervous!
Go for it! Go for it!
Thank you!Thanks!
Good work!
I'll do my best!
Good job!
I'll be running around, um, Yokohama? I'm looking forward to seeing the Red Brick Warehouse!
Oh, that's really great! You did great!
I'm so happy for you!
Good luck!
Genta Matsuda, hot!
Genta Matsuda, ah!
Genta Matsuda. And there was a high school boy on a bicycle.
Genta Matsuda, hang in there! like that.
Genta Matsuda, wow!
Genta Matsuda, you're hot!
Genta Matsuda, thank you! And then...
Genta Matsuda, what's your name? He said.
He said, "Genta Matsuda, I'm in a group called One Love Art! He said...
He said, "Genta Matsuda, artist-less! He said, "Genta Matsuda, artist-less!
Genta Matsuda, first time!
Genta Matsuda, hang in there!
Motota Matsuda, go for it!
Motota Matsuda, I'm doubles!
Genta Matsuda, you're hot! Really.
Motota Matsuda, hot!
Genta Matsuda, I can relate to many people.
I'm sure of it! Of course!
I have confidence in you, don't I? Yes, I do!
Yes, yes, yes!
Pisan. Pisan.
Pisan. Pisan.Pisan.
Nam-kun and others are younger than you, and Mu and others are younger than you.
We can't lose!
I will finish!
I will!
Bye bye!
First place!
Aaahhh!
Oh, hey, first place.
Oh, my God.
Sorry, first place.
This is pretty damning.
Listen...
I just saw a member walk by like this.
How's that possible?
I'm running to say hello to this member
I'm running to say hello to these members like this.
I was about to cry.
Oh, really?
It's so dull, so dull, so dull!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
It's really bad.
For the first time in my life.
I don't like the members.
It's not that I don't like them.
I don't hate them.
I don't like it.
Look, camera camera!
Camera, camera, camera.
They didn't see us.I'm through with the members.
Oh, my God!
Terrible, terrible, terrible, terrible, terrible, terrible!
Terrible, terrible, terrible, terrible!
The members, they said, "Number one.
They didn't even show up.
I'm so sad.
I'm going for a run.
One, I'm sorry.
One, sorry.
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God, oh, God, oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
I really don't want to do this anymore.
One, sorry.
Walk, walk, walk, walk.
One, I want to eat.
Do you want some water? Do you want some hocalin?
I'd like some water.
Oh!
It's hot.
It's cold.
I didn't get a chance to see you together.
Wow.
Sorry. Sorry.
But we just met.
Oh, man, this guy...
You just met him!
I'll definitely support you next time.
I'll be rooting for you.
Don't work so hard.
Half?Half?
I'm fine.
I got your back.
We're halfway there.
It's early.
It's early. It's really early.
Just keep moving and don't stop.
And don't hold on for any longer than you have to.
You should only hold on for a few more kilometers.
Really? - Yeah.
Just find me.
I'm really trying to help!
Have a good day!
Okay, good luck!
Hold on a second.
It's better this way.
Yeah, go for it!
Thank you!
Ichi-chan, where are you going now?
We're going to Red Brick Talk!
Whoo!
Which way?
Yay!
Yeah!
Good job, guys!
You look so happy!
Love One is
It's a place where I belong.
It's a place where I feel at ease.
I think it's a place where I feel as comfortable as I do with my family.I think it's a place where you can enter with as much ease as you would a family member.
Yes, ma'am.
To the left.
Left. Left.
Yes, next right.
Oh, thank you, Ishin. Seriously.
I didn't do anything.
Seriously, thank you. Really, thank you.
I just ran a one-kilometer class.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Good luck passing the baton.
Yes, sir.
Our princess...
Our princess is about to run the whole 10 kilometers.
Yay!
That's great!
It's perfect.
We're almost at the finish line, Yzda!
Can we count on you, Mr. Yajima?
Very promising.
Yes, I do.
I'm really nervous.
I'm so nervous.
Three more to go.
It's finally time.
A white T-shirt.
Oh, my God!
Look, that's the bus.
I think that's the bus.
Oh, there it is!
I see the goal!
Oh, no, here it comes!Oh no, here it comes.
He's running.
He's running!
Drive him in!
Whoa!
I'm going.
Can you do it? You can do it every time.
Can you do it?
I feel so sick.
I'm so nervous.
Seven already?
I cried because I had to use up all my energy.
I'm not crying.
We're taking the elevator.
We'll meet you over there.
Okay.
Here it comes!
Yeah!
Inge!
Inge, go!
Go, go, go!
Go, Inge!
Inge!
Come on!
Come on!Come on!
Go for it!
I'm off!
Oh no!
I'm going to pass the baton to my successor, after receiving the bond properly.
I think this is a milestone for all of us to pass on what we've built together in good condition until the end.
I think there is a bond that deepens.
I hope that I can carry that on my shoulders to the end.
Thank you for watching!